Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Volleyball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, motion pictures documenting volleyball
1993-1997
RU 992
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
15.5
(63 videotapes)
The materials consist of videotapes created by the Department of Athletics documenting volleyball at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of videotapes created by the Department of Athletics documenting volleyball at Yale.
College athletes; College sports; Volleyball; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University -- Volleyball; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Volleyball game videotapes, 1993-1997; Accession 2006-A-063
  - Delaware, 1994 October 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Hofstra, 1993 November 4 (Box 1)
  - New Hampshire, 1995 September 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Fairfield, 1995 September 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Marist, 1995 September 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Siena, 1995 September 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Delaware, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Georgetown, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
  - James Madison, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Lafayette, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Princeton, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Princeton, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Wagner, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Boston College, 1995 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Columbia, 1995 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Cornell, 1995 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Harvard, 1995 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Princeton, 1995 November 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Lehigh, 1995 November; videotape (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Siena, 1995 November; videotape (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Colgate, 1996 September 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Delaware, 1996 September 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
  - UNH, 1996 September 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Marist, 1996 September 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Sacred Heart, 1996 September 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Georgetown, 1996 September 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Hofstra, 1996 September 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Brown, 1996 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 28)
  - Columbia, 1996 October 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 29)
  - Fairfield, 1996 October 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 30)
  - Hartford, 1996 October 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 31)
  - Brown, 1996 October 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 32)
  - Dartmouth, 1996 November 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 33)
  - Dartmouth, 1996 November 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 34)
  - Lehigh, 1996 November 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 35)
  - Harvard, 1996 November; videotape (VHS) (Box 36)
  - Cornell, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 37)
  - Cornell, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 38)
  - Dartmouth, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)
  - Princeton, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 40)
  - Boise State, 1997 September 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 41)
  - University of San Francisco, 1997 September 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 42)
  - Saint Mary's, 1997 September 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 43)
  - San Jose University, 1997 September 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 44)
  - Army, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 45)
  - Brown, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 46)
  - Brown, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 47)
  - Bucknell, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 48)
  - Central, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 49)
  - Columbia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 50)
  - Columbia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 51)
  - Dartmouth, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 52)
  - Dartmouth, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 53)
  - Holy Cross, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 54)
  - LIU, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 55)
  - Lehigh, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 56)
  - Marist, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 57)
  - Princeton, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 58)
  - Northeastern, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - Penn, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 60)
  - Saint Francis, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 61)
  - Vermont, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 62)